你们在干什么？ 我们想填完字谜再去睡觉
-What are you guys doing up? -Finishing the crossword.
你知道一个六个字母的单词表示红色的是什么吗？
Do you know a six-letter word for "red"?
深红色（两个词并且是七个字母）
Dark red.
应该不是 不过你待会可以玩连点题（4-8岁小孩玩的游戏）
Wrong,but there's a connect-the-dots in here for you later.
褐红色呢？
Hey,how about maroon?
没错，你好聪明
Yes! You are so smart!
你们好可爱喔 我知道
You guys are so cute.I know.
好，明天早上见 好
See you in the morning.
我最喜欢跟你填字谜了 我也是
I love doing crossword puzzles with you.Me too.
赶快填完去睡觉 好
Now let's finish this and go to bed.Okay
只剩一个，三个字母的单词 不是小狗，是…
Only one left.Three-letter word. Not dog,but....
猫咪
Cat.
没错，你好聪明
You are so smart!
我爱你 我也爱你
I love you.I love you too.
本集播出：“警察”
The One with the Cop
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
寇妮考克斯
丽莎库卓
麦特勒布蘭
马修派瑞
大卫修蒙
还差小费 好，等等
We still need a tip.All right. Hold on.
有了…5分钱
I got it.Nickel.
还差多少？ 2块钱
-How much do we need? -Couple of bucks.
10分钱
Okay,dime.
你们继续聊，我要花一点时间
You guys keep talking. This could take a while.
等等，你们看
Wait,look it!
天哪，这是警徽
This is a police badge!
真酷，但警察来这里干嘛？ 这里又不卖甜甜圈
Cool. But why would a cop come in here? They don't serve doughnuts.
你能不能重来一次 我可以说个更好笑的
Could you discover the badge again? I can do better than that.
一定有人正在找那个警徽
I bet somebody's missing that badge.
没错，我应该送回去 我去警察局
I should take it back. But at the police station...
还可以看看十大通缉犯名单
...I'll check their 10 Most Wanted List.
我朋友丽西一直是排名第11的 今年也许会轮到她
My friend's been number 11 forever. This could be her year!
大家好 嗨乔伊
-Hey,you guys. -Hey,Joey.
那是我的衣服吗？
Is that my sweatshirt?
没错，对不起，我有点冷
Yes,it is. I'm sorry. I was cold.
没关系吧？
I hope it's okay.
你应该穿你男朋友的衣服
It's just that if you wear someone's sweatshirt...
我又不是你的男朋友
And I'm not him.
对不起，我现在就还你 不要了，上面会沾满莫妮卡的味道
I'm sorry. I'll give it back.It's gonna be all smelling like Monica.
你是说我很臭吗？
Do I smell bad?
不是，你有一股青草香
You smell like a meadow.
对不起
I'm sorry.
他是怎么了？
What's with him?
乔伊上次去青草地 他妈妈被猎人射杀了
The last time Joey went to a meadow his mother was shot by a hunter.
你看，我找到一个警徽
Look what I found. It's a police badge.
怎么会？我又没看到甜甜圈
What's that doing here? I don't see any doughnuts.
警察和甜甜圈啊
Cops and doughnuts. Come on.
如果是钱德说的 你们就会笑翻了
If Chandler had said it you'd all be on the floor.
警察、甜甜圈、我？
Cops,doughnuts? Me?
我还是不确定
I still don't know.
抱歉，我想买到理想的沙发
I want to make sure I bought the right couch,
我希望这张沙发能让人觉得 “小朋友，欢迎你”
one that says..."Kids welcome here,"
同时也能让人觉得 “来我身边吧”
but that also says"Come here to me."
什么？你对小朋友说那种话？
What? You say that to kids?
不是，“来我身边吧” 是对女士说的
The "Come here to me" is,you know,for the ladies.
这是张好沙发 但不是神奇沙发
Ross,honey,it's a nice couch,it's not a magic couch.
你的选择很正确
Well,you picked a great couch.
是吗？ 没错，请在这里签个名
-Yes？-Yes, Sign here,please.
没问题
Sure.
这是…运费几乎跟价格一样贵
The delivery charge is almost as much as the couch!
太荒谬了，他家离这里才三条街
That's ridiculous. He lives three blocks away.
算了，我自己搬就好，谢谢
I'll take it myself. Thank you.
瑞秋，来吧 好
All right,Rach,come on. Let's go.
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding?
才三条街，又不是很重 抬抬看，快
Come on. It's only three blocks. It's not very heavy. Try it.
哦，我可以
Oh,I can do it.
你们会很喜欢这张沙发的
You two will really enjoy that couch.
我们不是一对
We're not together.
好，难怪我觉得怪怪的
Something didn't quite add up there.
罗斯
Ross
这话是什么意思？ 罗斯
What's that supposed to mean? Ross
你，她
Well,you. Her.
她很…你知道 而你却…你知道
I mean,she's very...you know.And you're,like...you know?
虽然与你无关 但我们确实交往过
Not that it's any of your business,but we did go out.
真的？你们两个？
Really? You two?
对，瑞秋
Ya，Rach？
我现在不想讲这个 我抬着一张很重的沙发
I don't want to do this now. I'm carrying a heavy couch.
那就赶快告诉他
Then tell him quickly.
好，我们交往过 不只交往过
Fine. We went out.Not only did we go out...
还做过298次 罗斯
...we did it 298 times! Ross
我实在…你居然有在算？ 你真没用
You kept count? You are such a loser!
再没用你也做了298次
A loser you did it with 298 times!
对不起小姐 怎么了？
Excuse me,ma'am.
你不能在树上摁香烟
You can't put your cigarette out on a tree.
我可以，很方便
Yeah,I can. It worked well.
你不该这么做，别再这么做了
But you shouldn't. So don't ever do that again.
我不会了… 抽下一根烟之前不会
I won't. Till I have my next cigarette.
站住，纽约警察，别动 什么？
Hold it!N.Y.P.D. Freeze,punk!
没错，你被活逮了
That's right. You are so busted.
把她带走！
Book them.
你在跟谁说话？ 别挣扎了
-Who are you talking to? -Save it,red!
不想在笼子里过夜 就跟那棵树道歉
Apologize to the tree or spend the night in the slammer.
我才不跟一棵树道歉
I am not apologizing to a tree.
赶快道歉，否则我要叫人了
You apologize to the tree right now or I am calling for backup.
来人啊，来人啊
Backup! Backup!
对不起，对不起 别来了，别来了
I'm sorry! Sorry!Okay,cancel backup! Cancel backup!
罗斯，你不是说有电梯？
Didn't you say there was an elevator in here?
我是有说，但其实没有 来吧
Yes,I did,but there isn't. Here we go!
你要不要找个搬运工
Don't you think we should rethink the whole hiring movers thing?
才不要，他们会敲竹杠
No way. They're a rip-off.
而且他们会先看准东西 再回来偷
They check out your stuff and come back later and steal it.
是真的，我在日线报导上看过 我好喜欢日线报导
It's true. I saw it on Dateline. -Oh I love dateline
珍宝莉是我唯一想亲的女人
Jane Pauley is the one woman I would kiss.
我不知道… 瑞秋，专心一点好吗？
-There's just something about her. -Rach,can we concentrate?
好，只有你能讲
Yeah,fine. I listened to your dumb story.
往左，左，左…
Okay,go left.Left. Left.
已经没有左了
Okay,you know what? There's no more left left.
好，抬高到你的头上 你行的，你行的
Lift it straight up over your head.Straight up. You can do it!You can do it!
没问题吧？很好
Okay. You got it?
没问题吧？没问题吧？没问…
You got it,right? You got it,right? You got
你觉得放在那里好看吗？
Any chance you think it looks good there?
这家伙还不服气 我就说我是布菲，重案组的
This guy was all:And I'm all,"Buffay! Homicide!"
真是酷毙了
It was just so cool!
菲比，你应该拿去还的
-You were supposed to take it back.
我知道，但行善的感觉好棒
-I'm having fun doing good deeds.
但假扮警察很严重，你会被捉
You can get arrested for impersonating a police officer.
你现在就会被捉
You could get arrested right now!
我得拿去还 我被权力冲昏头了
I'd better take it back. I'm totally drunk with power.
乔伊 我不知道你们会在
Yeah. I didn't know you guys would be here.
乔伊，你尝尝看 什么？为什么？
-Do me a favor. Taste this. -What? Why?
放心，她是专业厨师
It's okay,Joe,she's a trained chef.
其实我要找菲比
Actually,I was looking for Phoebe.
你刚跟她擦身而过
Well,you just missed her.
那是她吗？我去追她
Was that her?I gotta go.
乔伊，等等，你是怎么了？
Joey,wait a minute. Wait.What is with you?
没事啊 拜托，你一整天都怪怪的
Nothing.You're acting strange.
好吧，是有一件事 我做了一个梦…
All right. There is something.I kind of had a dream.
但我不想谈
But I don't want to talk about it.
马丁路德金也这么说的话就麻烦了
What if Martin Luther King had said that?
我有一个梦…但是我不想谈
I kind of have a dream.I don't want to talk about it.
跟莫妮卡有关
Look,it involved Monica.
你梦到我在交往的女孩？真酷 我不知梦见他的女朋友多少次
You had a dream about the girl I'm seeing? Cool.I dreamt about the girls he was seeing.
总之我们在谈你的梦 我爱你…你的梦？
Let's talk about your dream. I love you. Your dream?
放心，没有任何性意味
There was no sex. I haven't dreamt of her like that...
自从发现你们的事 我就不对她做那种梦了
...since I found out about you two. More or less.
那你梦到什么？
What was the dream about?
好吧，你是我的女朋友
You were my girlfriend.
我们在填字谜 就像你们昨晚那样
We were doing the crossword puzzle.Like you did last night.
就这样，我爱上莫妮卡了 我会搬走
That's it. I'm in love with Monica. I'll move out.
乔伊等等，那并不代表你爱我
Joey,come on. That doesn't mean you're in love with me.
不是吗？ 它可能有很多涵义，例如…
It doesn't?It could mean anything. Like...
你突然眼红我成为这里的猛男
...you're jealous that I've become the apartment stud.
听起来比较像你的梦
Sounds like your dream.
或是你看到我和钱德很亲密 你也想跟别人拥有这种关系
Or it could mean you saw Chandler and me being close and stuff...and you want that too.
我在梦里的确很享受那种亲密
In the dream I did enjoy the closeness.
如果是这样就太好了 我就不必搬走了
If that's what it was,that'd be great. I wouldn't have to move.
你对莫妮卡着迷吗 此时此刻 你对莫妮卡有兴趣吗？
Are you attracted to Monica?Right here,right now,are you attracted to her?
其实没有 这就对了
-Not really. -There you have it!
是啊，我穿得这么随便
Well,sure! I'm just wearing sweats!
但那是好事，你不是爱我 你只是想交个女朋友
But that's good!You're not in love with me. You just want a girlfriend.
我觉得不是交女朋友的问题
It's not just about getting a girlfriend.
我可以找个女朋友 我们可以坐在那里填字谜
I could get a girlfriend. We could sit and do crossword puzzles.
但我们会拥有你们那种亲密吗
But could we have the closeness like you have?
莫妮卡和我是从朋友做起 也许关键在这里
Monica and I were friends before we dated. Maybe that's it.
先做朋友？有意思
Friends first?That's interesting.
你们是事后成为朋友吗？ 不，从来没有过
-You become friends after? -No,never done that either.
你们有量尺吗？ 有，在我房里
Do you guys have a tape measure?Yeah. It's actually in my bedroom.
没错
That's right.
乔伊，怎么了？
What's up,Joey?
你好吗？
How you doing?
抱歉，这是你的车吗？ 对
Excuse me. Is this your car?
停在这里不太好 你挡住出入口了
Don't park here. You're blocking the entrance.
放心，没关系的
Don't worry. It's not a problem.
我觉得有关系，你就有关系 因为我是警察
It's a problem for me,so it's a problem for you,because I'm a cop.
我也是
So am l.
完了
Oh no
好，你是警察，可以任意停车 这个我知道，因为我也是警察
Okay. So you're a cop. You can park anywhere.I know,because I'm a cop too.
好，继续努力，收到
Keep up the good work. 10-4.
等一下，你是哪个分局的？
Wait. So,what precinct are you with?
我在57分局 我认识你们重案组一位刑警
I'm with the 57th.-I know a guy in Homicide up there.
我在风化组
-I'm in Vice.
事实上我正在卧底，我是妓女
In fact,I'm undercover right now. I'm a whore.
风化组还有谁？
Who else is in Vice there?
你认识西波维茨吗？ （《纽约重案组》主角）
Do you know...Sipowicz?
西波维茨？应该不认识
Sipowicz? I don't think so.
西波维茨，大块头，有点秃
Yeah. Sipowicz. Yeah. Big guy,kind of bald.
我不认识他
I don't know him.
不要打给他 他不在，他出去了
Don't try to call him. He's not there. He's out.
他的拍档刚死了
His partner just died.
帮我跟西波维茨致意 我会的，保重
Tell Sipowicz I'm real sorry for his loss.I sure will. Take care.
对了
By the way,
我相信西波维茨不会有事的 听说那个《银匙》里的小伙子很不错
I'm sure Sipowicz will be all right. I heard that kid from Silver Spoons is really good.
你在哪里找到我的警徽的？
Where'd you find my badge?
乔伊 你能不能帮我和罗斯搬沙发？
Could you give me and Ross a hand moving his couch?
我很想，但我要去上表演课
I'd love to,but I got acting class.
可是，你知道吗 我可以为了你跷课
But you know what?I guess I could blow that off. For you.
谢谢 我问你一件事
Let me ask you something.
我刚在对面跟莫妮卡钱德聊天 他们可真亲密
I was talking with Monica and Chandler.Boy,they are really tight.
是啊 那种关系实在很不错
I know.That's not a bad situation they got there.
我也想自己弄一段
Think I'll get me one of those.
你想说什么？
What's up,Joe?
我觉得他们感觉会那么好 是因为他们是先做朋友
I think Monica and Chandler are so great...because they were friends first.
于是我问自己：谁是我朋友？ 你和菲比
So I asked myself,who are my friends? You and Phoebe.
而我先遇见你，所以…
I saw you first,so....
你在说什么？ 我是说也许你我可以更进一步
-What are you saying? -Maybe you and I crank it up a notch.
知道吗亲爱的 你先遇见我令我受宠若惊
You know,honey...as flattered as I am that you saw me first
但我不觉得我们应该更进一步
...I just don't think we should be cranking anything up.
我会对你很好
I'll treat you real nice.
你知道吗…
Yeah. Well,you know....
我觉得先做朋友再交往 是一个很好的想法
I think it's a great idea to become friends with someone before you date.
但你应该先去认识一个人 跟她做朋友
But the way you do it is you meet someone,become their friend...
建立基础，再约她出去
...build a foundation,then ask them out on a date.
别对现有的朋友下手
Don't hit on your existing friends.
那不是要很久？
Won't that take longer?
没错，但是一旦得到了 真的很值得
Oh,but once you find it...it's so worth the wait.
我懂，我懂
I understand.
真想先遇见菲比
Man,I wish I saw Phoebe first.
来我身边吧
Come here to me.
不，你来我身边
No,no. You come here to me.
罗斯，我带援军来了
-I brought reinforcements.
太好了，是乔伊吗？ 只比他差一点
-Great! You brought Joey?The next best thing.
你带钱德来？ 只差一点的是莫妮卡
You brought Chandler? The next best thing would be Monica!
你这么说我应该要生气的 但莫妮卡真的壮得可怕
I would be offended,but Monica is freakishly strong,so....
我画了一张搬运草图
I drew a sketch of how we'll do it.
瑞秋，这是你，这是沙发
Rach,that's you.That's the couch.
那是什么？ 那是我
What's that?That's me.
你把自己想得很雄伟喔
Certainly think a lot of yourself.
不，那是我的手臂
No. That's my arm.
我还以为你那么那么得喜欢你的新沙发呢
I see. I thought you just really,really liked your new couch.
总之听我的指示 好
Just follow my lead.
钱德，来吧
Come on,Chandler.
好，开始了
-All right. -Okay.Here we go.
可以了吗？ 可以
All right. Ready?
转，转，转
Turn!Turn!Turn!
应该是转不动了
-I don't think we can turn any more!
我觉得挤不上去 当然可以，快抬起来
-I don't think it'll fit!Yeah,it will. Come on! Up,up,up!
抬起来，很好，中心点
Up! Yes!Here we go! Pivot!
中心点
Pivot!
中心点，中心点
Pivot!Pivot!
闭嘴！闭嘴！闭嘴
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
我看是上不来了 是吗？
I don't think it'll pivot any more.You think?
搬下去再来一次
All right,let's bring it back down and try again.
现在真的卡死了
I think it's really stuck now.
居然没成功
-I can't believe that didn't work.
就是啊，你都画了图了
-I know. Me neither.I mean,you had a sketch.
你说中心点是什么意思？
What did you mean when you said "pivot"?
我就是转不出来
Man,I cannot figure this out.
因为现在不是1985年
Yeah,because it's not 1985.
你们知道吗？ 我刚甩掉一个警察
You guys,guess what? I ditched a cop.
什么意思？
-What? -What do you mean?
他逮到我用他的警徽然后想抓我 该死的真警察
He caught me using his badge and he tried to bust me.Damn real cops!
他追了你多远？
How far did he chase you?
其实没追 他捡起警徽之后就杵在那里
Well,he didn't really. He just picked up his badge and stood there.
也许你会上 “史上最无趣警匪追逐战”之类的节目
Maybe we'll see you on World's Most Boring Police Chases.
你为什么要跑？ 我非跑不可
-Why did you run? -I had to.
假扮警察是2到4年的重罪 我才不要回那个地狱
You know,impersonating a cop is like a Class E felony.Two to four years minimum. I am not going back to that hellhole.
要是能找出中心点 就能继续搬了
If I can just get it to pivot...we'll be back on track.
瑞秋，帮帮忙好吗？ 好
-Rach,can I get some help please? -Yeah.
快关掉
Turn it off! Turn it off!
也许消防队员可以帮你搬
Maybe the firemen can help us move the couch when they get here.
等等 这可是新沙发 是新沙发
-Wait,wait,wait. -It's a new couch! It's a new couch!
怎样？有交到新朋友吗？
How's it going? Make any new friends?
有，我认识了一个女人
Yeah. I met this woman.
她怎么样？
What's she like?
她的床上功夫很棒
Well,she's...really good in bed.
你不是要先当朋友吗？
-You were going to be friends first.
都是你的错 为什么？
-Hey,it's all your fault.Why?
你给的不是忠告，是怎么搭讪
You didn't give me advice. You gave me a pickup line.
我一说要建立基础，先当朋友
I told her I wanted to build a foundation and be friends first.
她突然就…与我本身无关 我觉得难以抗拒
Suddenly,through no fault of my own,I became irresistible to her!
她的室友也是
And her roommate.
那亲密关系呢？
What about the closeness?
亲密个头！我们三个叫成一团
Closeness,schmosness. There was three of us,for crying out loud!
谁要吃披萨？ 我要我要我要
Who wants pizza?I do! I do! I do!
太棒了！你相信这是我在二楼捡到的吗
This is great! Can you believe I found it on the second floor?
哪一位？ 纽约警察
-Who is it? -N.Y.P.D.
天哪 等一下，警察先生
Oh,my God!Just a minute,officer!
我要找菲比布菲
-I'm looking for Phoebe Buffay.
完了，是那个警察 他居然找到我了
-My God,it's him! It's that cop!-I can't believe he found me!
天哪，你会坐牢吗？
-Are you gonna go to jail?
我要死也要拖你们下水
If I go down,you guys go down with me.
窝藏逃犯起码要关1到3年
Harboring a fugitive? That's one to three years minimum.
钱德，祝你好运
Good luck,Chandler.
好，你可以逮捕我 但你抓不到我的把柄
Arrest me,but you'll never make it stick and you know it.
但我别无选择 这是职责所在，你了解吧？
I have no choice,it's my job. You understand,right?
你了解吗我会找我的律师来
And you understand that I'm calling my lawyer.
他会让你在法庭上像个傻帽 傻帽！
And once he puts you on the stand,he'll make you look like a fool!
我不喜欢当傻帽
I don't like looking foolish.
这样吧，我今天不捉你 就说我来了，但你不在
Maybe I don't arrest you today. Maybe I came by and you weren't here.
我不在就太好了
I'd love it if I weren't here!
既然你今晚不会入狱 我能不能请你去吃饭？
Since you're not going to jail tonight,I was wondering if you'd...Iike to go to dinner with me?
我？ 对
Me? Yes
自从你对我亮警徽 我就对你念念不忘
Ever since you flashed my badge I can't stop thinking about you.
你是我见过最美的假卧底妓女
You're the prettiest fake undercover whore I've ever seen.
漂亮
Nice.
我想不到你会约我出去
I didn't see that coming. You're asking me out.
我可以表现得更好 但这些人一直盯着我
I could've done it better,but these people keep staring at me.
我愿意跟你吃饭，警察先生
I'd like to go out with you,officer.
盖瑞  盖瑞
-Gary. -Gary.
那就这么说定了 好
Okay,so it's a date.
不过我一定要问 你是怎么找到我的？
I gotta ask you,though. How'd you find me?
我的警徽上都是你的指纹 我上电脑查询
I ran your fingerprints through the computer.
这是你最后登记的住址 所以我就来看看
This was listed as your last known address.
好厉害 没有你厉害
Impressive.Not as impressive as you.
我看过你的纪录 你干过不少怪事
Your record shows you've done some weird stuff.
吃饭时再说 好
We'll talk at dinner.
我2个小时后来接你？ 好，我好兴奋
-So I'll come by and pick you up? -I can't wait.
放心，我不会只带你吃甜甜圈
Don't worry,I won't just take you out for doughnuts.
他有枪耶
He has a gun!
我要退这张沙发 我对它不满意
I'd like to return this couch. I'm not satisfied with it.
你要退这张沙发？
You wanna return this couch?
它断成两半了
It's cut in half.
我就是这个意思
-That's what I'm telling you.
是你把它摔成两半的？
-Did you cut this couch in half?
很不可思议，它本来就这样
It's crazy,it is cut in half.
我不懂
I don't understand.
这张沙发断成两半 我要换一张没有断成两半的
This couch is cut in half.I would like to exchange it for one that is not cut in half.
弄成这样不能退货
We can't accept it in this condition.
弄成这样我也不能买
Well,I can't accept it in this condition.
你是说它送过去就这样了？
You're saying this couch was delivered to you like this?
我很讲道理 我愿意接受换购金额
Look,I'm a reasonable man.I will accept store credit.
我给你4元的换购金额
I'll give you store credit in the amount of four dollars.
我接受
I will take it.